## **PERSONAL DETAILS**



Address

1440 Roxas Blvd, Manila,

1005, Philippines

Phone number +1 (213) 342-8506

Email address jeyjy0810@gmail.com

Github github.com/JeyJy

## **LANGUAGES**

English ★★★★

#### **INTERESTS**

- Watching Football game
- Photography
- Sports

#### **MAIN SKILLS**

React	****
Next.js	****
Vue.js	****
Python	****
Javascript	****
Typescript	****
web3	****
PHP	****
Node	****
Express	****
CSS	****

# Jey Braun

## Senior Full-stack Developer

Senior Full-stack developer with 7+ years of hands-on experience in Web | Mobile development. Dedicated to keeping best practices and producing clean and maintainable code. Looking forward to enhancing my leadership skills and utilizing problem-solving abilities in a fast – growing industry. Able to effectively self-management during independent projects as well as collaborate as a part of a productive team.



### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Aug 2020 - Sep 2023

Senior Full-stack Developer

#### **JLABS**

- Used relation databases and NoSQL databases to streamline data for developing practical applications
- Developed 3 highly interactive web applications utilizing Javascript, HTML5, CSS, JSON, Angular, and Angular material while integrating Restful APIs and external web services, ensuring high performance
- Upgrade the REST API and integrate Google API to the original back-end

Apr 2017 - Feb 2020

Junior Software Engineer

#### **KMS Solutions**

- Build a lot of chatbot card components for design chatbot
- Implemented smart rendering algorithm for drawing a lot of chatbot diagrams
- Built chatbot center and widget for integration on customer websites
- Performed the Unit test and Acceptance test using Jest

) Jan 2015 -Jan 2017

#### React Front-End Developer

#### Tensei Philippines Inc

- Implemented new UI/UX using React, SCSS and Bootstrap.
- Integrated APIs using GraphQL and React Apollo.
- Developed reusable components with React and Storybook.
- Performed all levels of testing from Unit test to Acceptance test.



## **EDUCATION**

2012 - 2016

Computer Science and Software Engineering Polytechnic University of the Philippines

BSc Computer Science and Software Engineering include object oriented programming, AI and systems development.

# Jey Braun

**Senior Full-stack Engineer** 

## **SKILL HIGHLIGHTS**

Project management

**Strong Communication** 

Complex problem solver

Quick-Delivery of Work

Service-focused

Full-time & Hardworking



## **CERTIFICATIONS**



Jan 2021

BTA Certified Front-End Developer KPMG, London

Certified practical and theoretical knowledge of Front-End and Mobile Development





# **SKILLS**

Languages

JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, CSS3, HTML 5, Python, PHP

Back-End Frameworks:

Node.js, Express.js, Go, Laravel, Codeigniter, Nuxt.js, Django, Flask

Front-End Frameworks:

React, Next.js, Vue.js, Svelte, React Native, Web3, Angular, Tailwind CSS,

API

GraphQL, Rest API, Restful API

Storage

MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firebase, AWS, AWS Lambda